<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Conference</string>
    <string name="isft_details"><![CDATA[The International Symposium on Fusion of Science and Technology (ISFT) provides a forum to the best talents in the academia & research institutions, industry experts, management professionals, engineers and executives to collaborate and address the current challenges, to seek new windows for discovery and exploration, and to promote the new horizon of science, engineering & technology for a sustainable future. The conference is aimed to promote synergetic partnership between academia and industry and also to showcase the growth of cutting-edge technology developed in recent past. Each year ISFT receives more than 500 articles from the world over. Now ISFT 2020 is being held at Faridabad (NCR), India during January 6-10, 2020. ISFT was started in 2011 through the collegial relationship between South Korea and Thailand by the founders of ISFT, including Prof. Hanshik Chung, Dean, Mechanical and Energy Department, and Dr. Chulsu Kim, CEO of KTENG, from Korea and Assoc. Prof. Napat Watjanatepin and Mr. Manoon Chunchom from Thailand.Seven conferences have so far been organized.]]></string>
    <string name="ymca_details"><![CDATA[J.C. Bose University of Science and Technology, YMCA, Faridabad (erstwhile YMCA University of Science and Technology, Faridabad erstwhile YMCA Institute of Engineering, Faridabad) was established in the year 1969, as a joint venture of the National Council of YMCAs of India, Govt. of Haryana, and the Central Agencies for Development Aid, Bonn, Germany. It started as an Indo-German project to impart technical education to a developing India on German pattern. The labs & workshops have been set up with the assistance of German expertise. In 1996, State Govt. of Haryana took complete control of the Institute and upgraded it to University status in Dec. 2009. The university offers 4-year B.Tech degree course and has added new chapters in its glorious history i.e. M.B.A., M.C.A, M.Tech. (Computer Engineering, Electrical Engineering, Electronics Engineering & Mechanical Engineering), M.Sc. (Physics, Maths, Chemistry & Environmental Sciences), M.A.(Mass Communication and Journalism) and Ph.D. It follows it’s course curriculum duly approved by the industries and the University. The salient features of German education have been retained & as such the University stands apart from other colleges of Haryana.]]></string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>
